

DEEPAK SINGH PARMAR

Associate Software Engineer

+91 8815912618

deepaksinghparmar1999@gmail.com

https://deepaksinghparmar.github.io/pro

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Technology Truba Institue of Engineering 2018 - 2022

Bright Paragon Academy Intermediate (12th PCM) 2017 - 2018

Mansarovar Public School Hight School (10th)

2014 - 2015

EXPERTISE

- ReactJS & ReduxJS
- NextJS
- Html, Css & Jquery
- Javascript
- MongoDB
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Mysql
- Firebase
- Highcharts
- D3.JS
- Aggrid
- Material UI
- Ant Design
- Visual studio code
- Figma
- Git, Github & Gitlab
- Data visualization
- Data structures and algorithms

SOFT SKILL

- Team work
- Problem solving
- Quick learner

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi

INTERESTS

- Video games
- Cricket
- Sketching

PROFILE

Eager to join an organization for continuous learning and growth, I bring strong Node is expertise in building efficient server-side applications and RESTful APIs. With over 2+ years of experience in React development, I excel in creating user-friendly, responsive interfaces while embracing new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Netlink Software Pvt Ltd. | Bhopal

Associate Software Engineer

July 2022 – Present

- Part of the product team, Lumenore at Netlink Software Pvt. Ltd
- Building stable and maintainable codebase in ReactJS
- · Creating a reuseable UI component in ReactJS.
- Developed RESTful APIs in node.js and express.js for various modules of the product.
- · Performing bug fixes and code reviews.
- · Creating new features, functionality, and capability in the
- Developed new data visualizations, charts, grids etc...

Trainee Software Engineer

Aug 2021 - June 2022

- Worked on frontend & backend part of the product.
- Implemented modules like self-service, conditional formatting in tables and charts of the product.
- Developed RESTful APIs in node.js for various modules of the
- · Developed component library for easily sharing of generic components across the product

PROJECTS

- Lumenore reliable Intelligence delivered Lumenore helps businesses by tapping into their data universe and ramping up their performance and growth with a powerful, integrated decision intelligence platform.
- Clients: Birlasoft, Fordcredit, SiriusXM etc...

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Pinnacle Performer at Netlink Software Pvt. Ltd (Feb 2022) For valuable contribution, outstanding dedication and innate commitment towards company
- 6 Start Coder At Hackerrank (Problem Solving)
- 3 Start Coder At CodeChef
- 230+ Question Solved In LeetCode